<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<history>
    <change version="12" date="2014-07-26">
      - New PAMM-index "i500" added.
      - Improved the forecast of drawdown for PAMM indices.
    </change>
    <change version="11" date="2014-04-10">
      - Adaptation to the new code.
    </change>
    <change version="10" date="2014-04-07">
      - New PAMM-index "Million3" added.
      - Some improvements.
    </change>
    <change version="9" date="2014-03-22">
      - New PAMM-index "Prize2" added.
      - Some improvements in the forecast procedure.
    </change>
    <change version="8" date="2014-03-01">
      - Counter depended by PAMM indices added: Sum of open trades. It calculated by all PAMMs included in PAMM-index. Also, look for more details in provider's log.
      - Counters added both to PAMM-monitoring and PAMM indices sections: Forecast of drawdown. WARNING! THIS IS ONLY FORECAST, NOT RECOMMENDATION!
    </change>
    <change version="7" date="2014-02-24">
      - Added types of request: Personal account, PAMM-monitoring, PAMM indices.
      - Counters depended by PAMM-monitoring added: Trader initial capital, Trader current capital, Amount in management, Relative drawdown, Maximum drawdown, Number of open trades, Expected annualized gain, Previous rollover, Next rollover, Last month, Last month profit, Last month interest, Last week, Last week profit, Last week interest.
      - Counters depended by PAMM indices added: Index included, Time of starting, Last week, Last week return, This week, This week return.
      - Counter depended by Personal account added: Total equity. It calculates the sum of all accounts.
      - Counter changed: Income (as Total equity - Difference).
      - Counter removed: Leverage.
      - Units added for some counters.
      - Some fixes.
    </change>
    <change version="5" date="2014-02-14">
      - Counters added from the Summary payments table ('Make deposit' tab): Deposited, Withdrawn, Difference.
      - Counter added: Income (as Equity - Difference).
      - Some counters changed to optional.
    </change>
    <change version="4" date="2014-02-04">
      - Adaptation to the new design.
    </change>
    <change version="3" date="2014-01-22">
      - Some correct for Receipts.
    </change>
    <change version="2" date="2014-01-11">
      - Counter added: Receipts (as Equity - Balance).
      - Some error diagnostic added.
    </change>
</history>